[{"answer": "Dr. my friend is a great musician. He actively opposed the that place and later on he helped many Jews to escape", "docId": "takingsides.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "It was my friend. I was told he just made the maestro his Privy Councillor, no questions asked. Although Dr. my friend stood up to him. And to Dr. my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Oh, we didn't play for his birthday, we played the evening before", "docId": "takingsides.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Do I know my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I hear the British have his... his archive, files, records", "docId": "takingsides.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "How could I know what's in the archive", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I want you to understand why you're here. You're automatically banned from public life under that place Directive No 24. We're here to look into your case before you appear in front of the that place. You understand that", "docId": "takingsides.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What they do in that place doesn't interest me one little bit. Okay? I have your questionnaire here,  my friend, born that place, January 1886. Orchestral conductor. And you say here you were never a member of the that place", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I wrote an open letter to the newspapers condemning what they were doing to music, making these distinctions between Jews and no", "docId": "takingsides.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " I did not conduct at at the rally, I conducted on the evening before the rally", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "During an enforced hou", "docId": "takingsides.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "It would be truer to say, I think, that a lot of people in high places knew me", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " my friend", "docId": "takingsides.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Love 'em, my friend. I give up. What are you holding in your hand", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Was a member of...? Speak up", "docId": "takingsides.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Oh, I see, he made you c", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "He did", "docId": "takingsides.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "One of my people", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Where do you stand on all this", "docId": "takingsides.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "On Furtwngler", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I have no idea what you're talking about", "docId": "takingsides.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I never sent him any birthday greetings or any other kind of greetings", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Tell me about von der Null", "docId": "takingsides.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yes, von der Null", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " Von der Null", "docId": "takingsides.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Von der Null", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What is this, my friend", "docId": "takingsides.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "What's not right", "qsentId": 28}]